[Birds chirping]
Boy: Come here
[Sigh]
Boy: You know they say life is short They say you wake up one day and,
on that day, all of your dreams and everything you wished for and you wanted, they're gone, just like that.
You know?
People,
people get old, and you know things change and, and situations change and
What I want is, I just I want this moment right now, this day.
And my feelings for you and the way you look right now.
The way I look at you, I just want this to last forever you know.
Girl: And it will. I mean no matter what, we’ve always had this and had each other.
Now nothing can change that.
But I just want you to know no matter what, you have always somebody here for you
Always, and I’m never gonna leave you. I’m never gonna leave you.
I love you.
Boy: I know, I know. [Sigh]
Girl: Don’t ever leave me.
Boy: I won’t.
Boy: I won’t, I won’t.
♪♪
♪ Summer has come and passed ♪ ♪ The innocent can never last ♪
♪ Wake me up when September ends ♪
♪ Like my fathers come to pass ♪
♪ Seven years has gone so fast ♪ ♪ Wake me up when September ends ♪
♪ Here comes the rain again ♪ ♪ Falling from the stars ♪
♪ Drenched in my pain again ♪ ♪ Becoming who we are ♪
♪ As my memory rests ♪ ♪ But never forgets what I lost ♪
♪ Wake me up when September ends ♪
[Door creaks]
Girl: You didn’t. Tell me you didn’t.
Boy: Do what?
Girl: Tell me you didn’t do it.
Boy: Tell you what?
[Smack] Boy: Ahh.
Girl: Tell me you didn’t do it, please. Please tell me you didn’t do it.
[Sobbing] Oh my god, oh my god, oh my god, oh my god.
[Sobbing] Please, you didn’t do it, please don’t do it. [Sob] Please. [Sob] How could you do that and not tell me?
Boy: Don’t do this, don’t do this. I wanted to tell you.
Girl: I love you so much.
Boy: I love you, too.
Girl: [Sobbing] Don’t.
Boy: Stop, stop. Just listen.
Girl: [Sob] How could you do this to me? How could you do this? [Sob] Oh my god.
[Sob] Oh my god.
Boy: I thought of all the people, you would understand. Why don’t you understand? I did this for us.
I did this for us. This is supposed to make it easier. (Girl: Oh my god, oh god).
I thought you’d be proud of me. I thought at least of all people why I did this.
Girl: [Sobbing] Oh god, oh my god. [Door opens]
♪♪
♪ Summer has come and passed ♪ ♪ The innocent can never last ♪
♪ Wake me up when September ends ♪
♪ Ring out the bells again ♪
♪ Like we did when spring began ♪ ♪ Wake me up when September ends ♪
♪ Here comes the rain again ♪ ♪ Falling from the stars ♪
♪ Drenched in my pain again ♪ ♪ Becoming who we are ♪
♪ As my memory rests ♪ ♪ But never forgets what I lost ♪
♪ Wake me up when September ends ♪
♪♪
[Gunshots and explosions]
♪ Summer has come and passed ♪ ♪ The innocent can never last ♪
[Gunshots and explosions] ♪ Wake me up when September ends ♪
♪ Like my father's come to pass ♪ ♪ Twenty years has gone so fast ♪
♪ Wake me up when September ends ♪
♪♪
[Gunshots & explosions]
[Echoing from before] Girl: Just know, no matter what. You always have somebody here for you.
I’m never gonna leave you.
[Birds chirping] [Music fades out]